/**
 * @param { import("knex").Knex } knex
 * @returns { Promise<void> }
 */
module.exports = [
    {
        id:1,
        deck_id:11,
        question: 'For loop',
        answer: 'In computer science a for-loop or for loop is a control flow statement for specifying iteration.'
    },
    {
        id:2,
        deck_id:11,
        question: 'An alternative to an if statement',
        answer:'Switch Statement.'
    },
    {
        id:3,
        deck_id:11,
        question: 'Mutate' ,
        answer: 'In R programming, the mutate function is used to create a new variable from a data set.'
    },
    {
        id:4,
        deck_id:8,
        question: 'Proton',
        answer: 'A proton is a stable subatomic particle, symbol p , H⁺, or ¹H⁺ with a positive electric charge of +1 e.'
    },
    {
        id:5,
        deck_id:8,
        question: 'Neutron',
        answer:'The neutron is a subatomic particle, symbol n or n⁰ , which has a neutral charge, and a mass slightly greater than that of a proton.'
    },
    {
        id:6,
        deck_id:8,
        question: 'Cell mutatation',
        answer: 'Mutations can result from errors in DNA replication during cell division, exposure to mutagens or a viral infection.'
    },
    {
        id:7,
        deck_id:8,
        question: 'Absorption',
        answer: 'A process in which one substance permeates another. A fluid permeates or is dissolved by a liquid or solid. Skin absorption is a route by which substances can enter the body through the skin.'
    },
    {
        id:8,
        deck_id:10,
        question: 'Angle Bisector',
        answer: 'The line dividing an angle into two equal angles.'
    },
    {
        id:9,
        deck_id:10,
        question: 'Algorithm',
        answer:'A procedure or set of steps used to solve a mathematical computation.'
    },
    {
        id:10,
        deck_id:10,
        question: 'Bell Curve',
        answer: 'The bell shape created when a line is plotted using data points for an item that meets the criteria of normal distribution. The center of a bell curve contains the highest value points.'
    },
    {
        id:11,
        deck_id:9,
        question: 'E-commerce can be defined as:',
        answer: 'The use of the Internet and the Web to transact business.'
    },
    {
        id:12,
        deck_id:9,
        question: 'Network externalities are related to which of the following features of e-commerce technology?',
        answer: 'Universal Standards'
    },
    {
        id:13,
        deck_id:9,
        question: 'Supply management/Procurement',
        answer: 'Business activity that includes all purchasing activities plus the monitoring of all elements of purchase transactions'
    },
    {
        id:14,
        deck_id:12,
        question: 'Recessive',
        answer: 'An allele that only shows phenotypic effects in the presence of another recessive allele.'
    },
    {
        id:15,
        deck_id:12,
        question: 'Heterozygous',
        answer: 'A genotype containing two types of alleles.'
    },
    {
        id:16,
        deck_id:12,
        question: 'Homozygous',
        answer: 'A genotype containing one type of allele'
    },
    {
        id:17,
        deck_id:12,
        question: 'Dominant',
        answer: 'Having the ability to mask the effects of a recessive allele.'
    },
    
];